HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm
1892-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE).
HERE General Legal Office
6199/010 mf
10.89 cubic feet
98 microfilm reels
Proceedings, pamphlets, correspondence, contracts, microfilm.
8254445
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 01, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arrangement
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE); HERE General Legal Office
8254445
- Series Proceedings & Conventions.
  - 1st. New York, NY., 1892; 1 (Reel 1)
  - 2nd. Chicago, IL., 1893; 2 (Reel 1)
  - 3rd. St. Louis, MO, 1894; 3 (Reel 1)
  - 4th. Boston, MA, 1895; 4 (Reel 1)
  - 5th. Cincinnati, OH., 1896; 5 (Reel 1)
  - 6th. Detroit, MI., 1898; 6 (Reel 1)
  - 7th. Chicago, IL., 1899; 7 (Reel 1)
  - 8th. Cleveland, OH., 1900; 8 (Reel 1)
  - 9th. St. Louis, MO., 1901; 9 (Reel 1)
  - 10th. Louisville, KY., 1902; 10 (Reel 1)
  - 11th. Philadelphia, PA., 1903; 11 (Reel 1)
  - 12th. Rochester, NY., 1904; 12 (Reel 1)
  - 13th. Kansas City, MO., 1905; 13 (Reel 1)
  - 14th. Toledo, OH., 1907; 14 (Reel 1)
  - 15th. Minneapolis, MN., 1909; 15 (Reel 1)
  - 16th. Boston, MA., 1911; 16 (Reel 1)
  - 17th. Denver, CO., 1913; 17 (Reel 1)
  - 18th. San Francisco, CA., 1915; 18 (Reel 1)
  - 19th. St. Louis, MO., 1917; 19 (Reel 1)
  - 20th. Providence, RI., 1919; 20 (Reel 1)
  - 21st. Cleveland, OH., 1921; 1 (Reel 2)
  - 22nd. Chicago, IL., 1923; 2 (Reel 2)
  - 23rd. Montreal, Que., 1925; 3 (Reel 2)
  - 24th. Portland, OR., 1927; 4 (Reel 2)
  - 25th. Kansas City, MO., 1929; 5 (Reel 2)
  - 25th. Constitution Revised., 1931; 6 (Reel 2)
  - 25th. Constitution Revised by Referendum., 7 (Reel 2)
  - 26th. Boston, MA., 1932; 8 (Reel 2)
  - 27th. Minneapolis, MN., 1934; 9 (Reel 2)
  - 28th. Rochester, NY., 1936; 10 (Reel 2)
  - 29th. San Francisco, CA., 1938; 1 (Reel 3)
  - 30th. Cincinnati, OH., 1941; 2 (Reel 3)
  - 31st. Milwaukee, WI., 1947; 3 (Reel 3)
  - Retakes Added Onto End of Roll, 4 (Reel 3)
  - 32nd. Chicago, IL., 1949; 1 (Reel 4)
  - 33rd. Atlantic City, NJ., 1953; 2 (Reel 4)
  - 34th. Chicago, IL., 1957; 3 (Reel 4)
  - 34th. Chicago, IL. (continued)., 1957; 1 (Reel 5)
  - 35th. Philadelphia, PA., 1961; 2 (Reel 5)
  - 36th. St. Louis, MO., 1966; 3 (Reel 5)
  - 37th. Chicago, IL., 1971; 4 (Reel 5)
  - Special Convention. San Francisco, CA., 1974; 5 (Reel 5)
  - 38th. Palm Springs, CA., 1976; 1 (Reel 6)
  - 39th. Chicago, IL., 1981; 2 (Reel 6)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 7)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 8)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 9)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 10)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 11)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 12)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 13)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 14)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 15)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 16)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 17)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 18)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 19)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 20)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 21)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 22)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 23)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 24)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 25)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 26)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 27)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 28)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 29)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 30)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 31)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 32)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 33)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 34)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 35)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 36)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 37)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 38)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 39)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 40)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 41)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 42)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 43)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 44)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 45)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 46)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 47)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 48)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 49)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 50)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 51)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 52)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 53)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 54)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 55)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 56)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 57)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 58)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 59)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 60)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 61)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 62)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 63)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 64)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 65)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 66)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 67)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 68)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 69)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 70)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 71)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 72)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 73)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 74)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 75)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 76)
  - General Office., 1 (Reel 77)
  - General President. Legislative Files., 1 (Reel 78)
  - General President. Pension Files., 1 (Reel 79)
  - General President. Pension Files., 1 (Reel 80)
  - General President. Pension Files., 1 (Reel 81)
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Bonding Records Files.
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1966; 1 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1967; 2 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1968; 3 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1969; 4 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1970; 5 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1971; 6 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1972; 7 (Reel 82)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1973; 1 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1974; 2 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1975; 3 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1976; 4 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1977; 5 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1978; 6 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1979; 7 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1980; 8 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1981; 9 (Reel 83)
  - U.S.F. & G. Company. Correspondence., 1982; 1 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Records., 1975-1978; 2 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 1 through 25., 1961-1982; 3 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 26 through 50., 1961-1982; 4 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 51 through 75., 1961-1982; 5 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 76 through 100., 1961-1982; 6 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 101 through 125., 1961-1982; 7 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 126 through 150., 1961-1982; 8 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 151 through 175., 1961-1982; 9 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 176 through 200., 1961-1982; 10 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 201 through 225., 1961-1982; 11 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 226 through 250., 1961-1982; 12 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 251 through 275., 1961-1982; 13 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 276 through 300., 1961-1982; 14 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 301 through 325., 1961-1982; 15 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 326 through 350., 1961-1982; 16 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 351 through 375., 1961-1982; 17 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 376 through 400., 1961-1982; 18 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 401 through 425., 1961-1982; 19 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 426 through 450., 1961-1982; 20 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 451 through 475., 1961-1982; 21 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 476 through 500., 1961-1982; 22 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 501 through 525., 1961-1982; 23 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 526 through 550., 1961-1982; 24 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 551 through 575., 1961-1982; 25 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 576 through 600., 1961-1982; 26 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 601 through 625., 1961-1982; 27 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 626 through 650., 1961-1982; 28 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 651 through 675., 1961-1982; 29 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 676 through 700., 1961-1982; 30 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 701 through 725., 1961-1982; 31 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 726 through 750., 1961-1982; 32 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 751 through 775., 1961-1982; 33 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 776 through 800., 1961-1982; 34 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 801 through 825., 1961-1982; 35 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 826 through 850., 1961-1982; 36 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 851 through 875., 1961-1982; 37 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Locals 876 through 900., 1961-1982; 38 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. Joint Executive Board., 1961-1982; 39 (Reel 84)
  - Blanket Bond Questionnaires. State Councils., 1961-1982; 40 (Reel 84)
  - Record of International Audits Received, 1960-1966; 41 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 1 through 25., 42 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 26 through 50., 43 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 51 through 75., 44 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 76 through 100., 45 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 101 through 125., 46 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 126 through 150., 47 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 151 through 175., 48 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 176 through 200., 49 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 201 through 225., 50 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 226 through 250., 51 (Reel 84)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 251 through 275., 1 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 276 through 300., 2 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 301 through 325., 3 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 326 through 350., 4 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 351 through 375., 5 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 376 through 400., 6 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 401 through 425., 7 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 426 through 450., 8 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 451 through 475., 9 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 476 through 500., 10 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 501 through 525., 11 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 526 through 550., 12 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 551 through 575., 13 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 576 through 600., 14 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 601 through 625., 15 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 626 through 650., 16 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 651 through 675., 17 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 676 through 700., 18 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 701 through 725., 19 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 726 through 750., 20 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 751 through 775., 21 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 776 through 800., 22 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 801 through 825., 23 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 826 through 850., 24 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 851 through 875., 25 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Locals 876 through 900., 26 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Joint Executive Board. A-C., 27 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Joint Executive Board. D-G., 28 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Joint Executive Board. H-M., 29 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Joint Executive Board. N-R., 30 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Joint Executive Board. S-T., 31 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. Joint Executive Board. U-Z., 32 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. State Councils. A-H., 33 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. State Councils. I-N., 34 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. State Councils. O-S., 35 (Reel 85)
  - Bond Cards. State Councils. T-Z., 36 (Reel 85)
- Series General President. AFL-CIO Files.
  - AFL-CIO Conventions., 1971; 1 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions., 1973; 2 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions. (AFL-CIO)., 1975; 3 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions. (Maritime)., 1975; 4 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions. (Union Label)., 1975; 5 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions. (Expense Sheets)., 1975; 6 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions., 1977; 7 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions., 1979; 8 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions., 1981; 9 (Reel 86)
  - AFL-CIO Conventions., 1983; 10 (Reel 86)
  - Building and Construction Trades., 1979-1982; 11 (Reel 86)
  - Civil Rights, Department of., 1976-1982; 12 (Reel 86)
  - C.O.P.E., 1974-1982; 13 (Reel 86)
  - Community Services, Department of., 1978-1982; 14 (Reel 86)
  - Donahue, Thomas, Sect.-Treas., 1981-1982; 15 (Reel 86)
  - Hanley, Edward, Vice-President., 1976-1982; 16 (Reel 86)
  - Education, Department of., 1976-1982; 17 (Reel 86)
  - Executive Council., 1981-1982; 18 (Reel 86)
  - Houston Campaign., 1981-1982; 19 (Reel 86)
  - Industrial Unions., 1976-1982; 20 (Reel 86)
  - International Affairs, Department of., 1973-1982; 21 (Reel 86)
  - Kirkland, Lane, President., 1982; 22 (Reel 86)
  - Legislation, Department of., 1975-1982; 23 (Reel 86)
  - Maritime Trades., 1974-1982; 24 (Reel 86)
  - George Meany Labor Institute., 1978-1982; 25 (Reel 86)
  - General President. AFL-CIO Files., 1 (Reel 87)
  - General President. Food & Beverages Files., 2 (Reel 87)
  - General President. Food & Beverages Files., 1 (Reel 88)
  - General President. N.C.C.M.P. Files, 2 (Reel 88)
  - General President. Gibson Trial Transcripts., 1 (Reel 89)
  - General President. Legal Files., 1 (Reel 90)
  - General President. Legal Files., 1 (Reel 91)
  - General President. Legal Files., 1 (Reel 92)
  - General President. Legal Files., 1 (Reel 93)
  - General President. Legal Files., 1 (Reel 94)
  - General President. Legal Files, Venn., 2 (Reel 94)
  - General President. Legal Files, Venn., 1 (Reel 95)
  - General President. National Contract Files., 1 (Reel 96)
  - General President. Legal. (Original), 1 (Reel 97)
  - General President. Legal., 2 (Reel 97)
  - General President. Contracts. (Original), 1 (Reel 98)
  - General President. Contracts., 2 (Reel 98)